Well, the last time I cried was during an intense emotional experience
because I felt I was losing something in my life
but at the same time I was gaining something else
or I was recovering something much more important in my life
which was recovering myself
sometimes losing certain things in life
isn't losing but is also gaining
so at a certain moment I felt like I was losing
something that maybe symbolized a lot to me
but that was also keeping me trapped
tied down and cut off from some things that made me exist
as a person
so I was crying
but at the same time reflecting
that just as I was losing
I was recovering
or gaining that freedom
to be able
to come back to myself